const questions = [
    {
      question: "1. Which of the following scoping type does JavaScript use?",
      choices: ['a) Sequential', 'b) Segmental', 'c) Lexical', 'd) Literal'],
      answer: 'c) Lexical'
    },
    {
      question: '2. Which of the following explains correctly what happens when a JavaScript program is developed on a Unix Machine?',
      choices: ['a) will work perfectly well on a Windows Machine', 'b) will be displayed as JavaScript text on the browser', 'c) will throw errors and exceptions', 'd) must be restricted to a Unix Machine only'],
      answer: 'a) will work perfectly well on a Windows Machine'
    },
    {
      question: '3. Which of the following can be used to call a JavaScript Code Snippet?',
      choices: ['a) Function/Method','b) Preprocessor','c) Triggering Event','d) RMI'],
      answer: 'a) Function/Method'
    },
    {
      question: '4. Which of the following object is the main entry point to all client-side JavaScript features and APIs?',
      choices: ['a) Position', 'b) Window', 'c) Standard', 'd) Location'],
      answer: 'b) Window'
    },
    {
      question: '5. Where is Client-side JavaScript code is embedded within HTML documents?',
      choices: ['a) A URL that uses the special javascript:code', 'b) A URL that uses the special javascript:protocol', 'c) A URL that uses the special javascript:encodingt', 'd) A URL that uses the special javascript:stackI'],
      answer: 'b) A URL that uses the special javascript:protocol'
    },
    {
      question: '6. Which of the following is not javascript data types?',
      choices: ['a) Null type', 'b) Undefined type', 'c) Number type', 'd) All of the mentioned'],
      answer: 'd) All of the mentioned'
    },
    {
      question: '7. Arrays in JavaScript are defined by which of the following statements?',
      choices: ['a) It is an ordered list of values', 'b) It is an ordered list of objects', 'c) It is an ordered list of string', 'd) It is an ordered list of functions'],
      answer: 'a) It is an ordered list of values'
    },
    {
      question: '8. Which of the following is correct about JavaScript?',
      choices: ['a) JavaScript is an Object-Based language', 'b) JavaScript is Assembly-language', 'c) JavaScript is an Object-Oriented language', 'd) JavaScript is a High-level language'],
      answer: 'a) JavaScript is an Object-Based language'
    },
    {
      question: '9. Among the given statements, which statement defines closures in JavaScript?',
      choices: ['a) JavaScript is a function that is enclosed with references to its inner function scope', 'b) JavaScript is a function that is enclosed with references to its lexical environment', 'c) JavaScript is a function that is enclosed with the object to its inner function scope', 'd) None of the mentioned'],
      answer: 'b) JavaScript is a function that is enclosed with references to its lexical environment'
    },
    {
      question: '10. What is JavaScript?',
      choices: [
        'a) JavaScript is a scripting language used to make the website interactive',
        'b) JavaScript is an assembly language used to make the website interactive',
        'c) JavaScript is a compiled language used to make the website interactive',
        'd) None of the mentioned'
      ],
      answer: 'a) JavaScript is a scripting language used to make the website interactive'
  }
  ]
  